Tsuwabuki-kun.
Yes?
I'll ask just in case, but...
Right now...
What month is it?
Umm, what month you say?
It's May.
Right now, it's November... Tsuwabuki-kun.
Just as I expected, your memory is in a mess.
This must be the effect of being exposed to magic from Figurare too many times.
Is something going to happen to me?
When all seven star drops are gathered,
I will then use them to concoct a medicine to return you to normal as Tsuwabuki Masaharu.
But at the same time,
you will forget everything that happened this past half year, Tsuwabuki-kun.
You will forget all that time that you shared with Sumomo-chan.
Everything.
Umm... Err....
Yuki-chan.
Err, the Yuki-chan that I slept together with,
bathed together, and also kissed...
Umm...
is actually Haru-kun?
Yes.
That's so...!
What are you doing, Sumomo?
This is so embarrassing!
Haru-kun saw me too...
No I didn't! Well I did, but...
How can I say this... During that time, it was kind of different.
I was Yuki-chan, so...
Umm... so that is...
So you did see...
Right, I haven't told Sumomo anything about what Kisaragi-sensei told me.
If you stay as you are and don't do anything,
the time will come when you will permanently stay as a doll.
You don't have any other choice here.
Sumomo...
A few months passed without me telling her about it.
So, Sensei, with these past six months...
...you're saying that Tsuwabuki... will forget all of it?
Even about him seeing Sumomo?
That's... cruel.
Sumomo...
It was my fault!
Everything was... my fault.
Yuuki, it's not like that.
Yaeno-san...
Sumomo and Tsuwabuki definitely don't hate or blame anyone.
That is why those two managed to make it this far.
Saying that the reason why Sumomo-chan, who never used a Ladle before was able to excel at using it...
...was because of a sheep doll, did sound unusual.
It was certainly strange even to me.
But now, I am sure of it.
They are both each other's strength.
The kindness that is shared between them became a miracle.
Yes.
It's somewhat strange, but yet, it happened like that.
And then...
Sumomo?
Haru-kun, the star drop will fall down tonight.
The seventh star drop will come!
Finally...
Sumomo...
I'm home!
Welcome!
Just kidding.
Well, I'm happy...
because Haru-kun is in my room.
Sumomo...
Umm, tonight, Dad will be at an event so no one else will be home.
He said it might be pretty scary, so it'd be better just to stay at home...
Ahh! By staying, he didn't mean like staying for the night or anything...
W-What am I saying...!?
Sumomo...!
Umm, so we'll finally be able to gather all seven star drops.
The seventh star drop will come from that side.
The day we've been waiting for has finally come, hasn't it?
We've gathered them one by one.
Puruvu Radi!
Always together with Yuki-chan...
Always being encouraged by Yuki-chan...
And being given courage by Yuki-chan.
Thank you, Yuki-chan.
There were some hard times too during this past half year, but it was fun.
It's too bad we can't be together tonight to capture the seventh star drop since it's a new moon.
It's kind of lonely because we can't meet, but...
This time, I can be together with Haru-kun for the whole evening.
I hope that like I did with Yuki-chan, Haru-kun will have fun too.
Sumomo...
Well, it won't be as mysterious as before, but...
Sumomo, I have to tell you something!
Haru-kun?
There is something that I haven't told you, Sumomo.
When we gather the star drops... all seven of them...
After that...
After that happens...
I'm sorry... I'll...
So something will happen...
Something sad...
I had this premonition...
Because everything has been going all too well with Haru-kun.
That perhaps it's all just a dream... and that everything will disappear when I open my eyes.
I felt afraid...
That when we would capture the final star drop...
Haru-kun would disappear.
It felt like...
Sumomo...
Sumomo!
When all seven star drops are gathered...
After drinking the medicine and returning to normal...
I...
will forget everything!
Everything!
From the moment I turned into Yuki-chan...
...and everything after that.
The time we spent together...
My feelings...
I will forget... just about everything.
The first time going home together...
We planted a lot of hydrangeas, didn't we?
I got to talk to Haru-kun when we were alone together.
My heart felt like it skipped a beat.
It was always beating so fast.
You're going to forget... everything?
I... I don't want you to.
I don't want you... to forget.
No, I don't want this.
Haru-kun, Haru-kun!
Sumomo...
I don't want to forget either!
I don't want to forget...
about you, Sumomo.
Haru-kun...
This is...
It seems like it's encouraging us...
saying "Don't cry"...
and that the seventh star drop is waiting.
That's right!
Haru-kun needs to return to normal.
Sumomo...
Before I forget just about everything,
I want to imprint Sumomo's figure in my heart.
Being as lovely as she is,
will I really forget these feelings?
Sumomo...
Haru-kun...
If only this moment would last longer, even by just a second.
If only our time lasted longer by even just a second.
It would be good if time could just stop.
It's too bad... We don't really remember which boat we used that day.
That time, I was really shy and embarrassed, so I was at a loss of what to say.
Me too!
They were in full bloom at that time...
That's right, Sumomo. Remember the bell?
The Bell of Hope, right? Let's go take a look.
Okay!
When the bell rings while a couple is together...
Umm...
the couple's future will be connected.
The bell which we didn't ring that day...
After that we just sat down together without saying anything...
...until the last moment.
The ring is...
Haru-kun, let me see your cell phone.
I'll delete all the messages that I've sent to you and also my e-mail address, okay?
That way, you don't feel strange looking at it later.
Eh, Sumomo?
It was only for two months, but there is a lot here already.
The star drop!
The other star drops too...
Sumomo.
Sumomo, listen.
Y-Yes?
Even if I forget everything, I... I will...
I will love Sumomo once again. I know it!
Yes!
It's a promise.
Yes. I'll be waiting, then.
I'll wait without crying.
Good morning!
Are you serious?!
I see...
What does that mean?!
Is it true that Tsuwabuki-kun lost his memory?
Yes.
I don't know the details, but according to Kisaragi-sensei,
Tsuwabuki lost all of his memory of this past half year.
This past half year?
T-Then, what about his going out with Sumomo?
T-Then he really forgot everything?
This can't be! Seriously?!
No way...
Let's tell him everything about this past half year!
That's right, let's do it together!
No, you shouldn't.
No, you shouldn't do it now.
It's better if we don't tell Tsuwabuki anything.
If we confuse him now, there's a chance it'll get worse.
Haru...
I feel bad for Sumomo-chan.
I won't cry...
because... because Haru-kun made a promise to me.
Haru-kun...
A-Are you all right?
I'm sorry.
Tsuwabuki-kun...
Umm... Well, I'm...
That is...
I'm sorry too, Tsuwabuki-kun.
How do you know my name?
We're in the same class.
I-I see.
Well then...
Haru-kun...
I believe in you, so...
It's a promise, so I'll wait and I won't cry...
...Haru-kun.
Aww, the last episode is already here.
That can't be!
It'll be so sad for Sumomo if things keep on going like this!
Please God let them be happy together!
That's right, Haru!
I'll not forgive you if you make a cute girl like her cry!
Yes, unforgivable!
They will definitely have a happy ending!